me
Please come and join us, we are Yugi Dokuson!
The theme is "Play Part Fun Friends" with a lot of live music.
It's a kind of event with a live performance.
I have a design that was done by one of the members before, and I used it as a base.
I'm not sure if this is the right mood, but I'd like to have each person put a different detail on the wind blunt.
If you wear it, you'll look like this character.
This is it. A bad one.
Thank you for your hard work.
I know, right?
Tongue.
Lately koreice ・Olympics
Unfamiliar
Thank you very much!
Yes, today's winner!
ni
Cute!
So cute!
I like it.
That's great.
This is my character of beeba borongo
Each of them will be designed
Cute!
It's a stuffed animal.
It's okay, I guess.
That's great.
That's too good. Thank you very much.
It's like he's got a pointy chin.
He's so cute.
It's cute.
Do you have a left or right side?
No, I don't.
Look at that.
Oh, you got a kiss?
That's so cute.
Do the ex-pal pose.
Oh, that's so cute.
He's cute.
You look good.
Do I look good?
Yeah, it looks good.
But I don't know if I'm gonna win this.
You're right.
Is that orange?
I'd like to wear it.
I want to wear this one, too.
I want to wear 12 of these.
I'll drop it in the future.
And that's it.
Thank you very much.
I'm so excited.
Which one do you think will win?
I think this one.
This one, this one.
Would you like to see all the logos?
Oh, I'd love to see them.
Aren't they super cute?
Cha-cha-cha-cha.
You can move surprisingly well, can't you?
Yes, I can.
It's adorable.
When I explained it to you, you really imagined it in your brain.
It's as if you've put out your brain exactly as I'd imagined it.
It's like you made it exactly as I imagined it in my brain.
I'm really, really happy.
It's so cute!
First of all, this Borongo's face.
Mr. Jimbo designed this face.
You can become Borongo, the official character of FC Beaver Borongo!
This is the second great thing about it!
It has a lower jaw.
This is better for the table.
I think there are hats like this at sports parks.
You can be more like Borongo with this hat!
3.
Hand
So cute!
Fluffy
Fluffy here, too.
Four.
Teeth on the inside here.
Even the teeth are cute!
The teeth are different for each member.
Eyes are also different.
And this hair is also different.
They even put their hands on.
It's a little bit like an image.
like a costumed gal.
Don't be afraid to get stuck in.
She's a bit stuck-up.
like a costumed gal.
I was trying to give you an image
and the fusion of that and the stuffed animal
It's perfect.
It's all so cute.
Isn't it super cute?
And this one, too.
Jimbo's design of Borongo.
and
It's so similar to the painting.
It's just like this.
His legs are like this.
This crotch hair...
It looks just like hers.
It's amazing!
It's just like it was.
I can do a jumper report.
13 Borongos.
Absolutely adorable!
Absolutely adorable.
Okay, only on tour.
You'll never see them.
You won't see them.
Special.
You're not going to be able to see
This...
Did you think I was asleep?
Oh, yeah.
Very special.
This borongo
Please vote for the park!
Isn't he cute?
There are 13 of them.
I hope you enjoy them.
I thought I wanted to go to bed.
Did you want to have a breakdown already?
Surprise!
Oh, I just did.
I'm seriously overthinking this.
I can't think about it too much.
You know what?
I wanted to give up.
I wanted to give up so badly.
It makes people nervous.
Oh, my God.
I want to be this
But I'm also a great opponent.
They're all cute.
You know...
Appeal.
I'll do my best in the event
Appeal
I will do my best
The video is
I recommend it.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel.
See you soon!